<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>sav_library</csh_table>
		<description>Default TCA_DESCR for extensions built with the SAV Library</description>
		<labelContext type="array">
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="helpGeneral.description">Help for General Tab</label>
			<label index="helpGeneral.details">&lt;b&gt;Select form&lt;/b&gt;
         use this selector to select the form name. Let use recall that the &quot;SAV Library&quot; makes it possible to build several forms associated with the same extension, thus providing different views of your tables.

        &lt;b&gt;Show all if no filter&lt;/b&gt;
        If set, all items are displayed if no filter is applied, for example by means of the &quot;sav_filter_abc&quot; extension.
        
        &lt;b&gt;If no information available&lt;/b&gt;
        Use the selector to choose what to display when no information are available.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Max number of items&lt;/b&gt;
        Maximum number of items that will be displayed in a page. If set to 0, all items are displayed.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Help page&lt;/b&gt;
        Use this selector to choose a page of your site which will be use as an help page for your extension. In this case, an icon is displayed in the title bar of your extension.</label>
			<label index="helpInput.description">Help for Input Tab</label>
			<label index="helpInput.details">&lt;b&gt;Input on form&lt;/b&gt;
        If set, Front End inputs are allowed.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Allowed groups&lt;/b&gt;
        If you select user groups, user must belong to one of these groups to be allowed to input data in the Front End.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Input Admin field&lt;/b&gt;
        Put here a field under the form &quot;tablename.fieldname&quot; (if you use only &quot;fieldname&quot;, the main table is taken as &quot;tablename&quot;).
        This will restrict the input to users that have &quot;Admin&quot; right for this field in their TS Config.
        For example, if one user has &quot;extKey_Admin=value1,value2&quot; in his TS Config, he will be allowed to edit or delete items for which &quot;fieldname&quot; is equal to &quot;value1&quot; or &quot;value2&quot; for the extension &quot;extKey&quot;.
        The fields or the folders which have the attribute &quot;editAdminPlus= 1;&quot; can be modified if the user has the &quot;Admin+&quot;&quot; rights. For example, if the TS Config is &quot;extKey_Admin=value1+,value2&quot; , the user is an &quot;Admin+&quot; for the records where &quot;fieldname&quot; is equal to &quot;value1&quot; and just &quot;Admin&quot; for the records where &quot;fieldname&quot; is equal to &quot;value2&quot;.
        Users become &quot;Super Admin&quot; for the extension &quot;extKey&quot; their TS Config is &quot;extKey_Admin=*&quot;&quot;.

        &lt;b&gt;No &quot;new&quot; button&lt;/b&gt;
        No new button is added to the form. It means that you can modify existing records but you cannot create new record.
        
        &lt;b&gt;No &quot;delete&quot; button&lt;/b&gt;
        A delete button will not be added in front of the records in &quot;show All&quot; views.

        &lt;b&gt;No &quot;edit&quot; button&lt;/b&gt;
        An edit button will not be added in front of the records in &quot;show All&quot; views.

        &lt;b&gt;Add a &quot;delete&quot; button only for records created by the user&lt;/b&gt;
        Add a &quot;delete&quot; button only for records created by the user.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Input start date&lt;/b&gt;
        If set,  inputs in the Front End will not be possible before this date.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Input end date&lt;/b&gt;
        If set, inputs in the Front End will not be possible after this date.

        &lt;b&gt;Apply date limit&lt;/b&gt;
        Use the selector to set either &quot;Nobody&quot;, &quot;All&quot;, &quot;Admin plus users&quot;, &quot;All excludind Super Admin&quot;. The date limit is applied according to this selector.</label>
			<label index="helpAdvanced.description">Help for Advanced Tab</label>
			<label index="helpAdvanced.details">&lt;b&gt;Permanent filter&lt;/b&gt;
        You can use this field to add a where clause that will be added to the where clause of the form query.

        &lt;b&gt;Add a fragment (# content id) to links&lt;/b&gt;
        The content id is added as a fragment to the links.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Allow the use of the &quot;query&quot; property&lt;/b&gt;
        The &quot;query&quot; property makes it possible to execute queries in &quot;input&quot; or &quot;update&quot; forms.
        Because any query may be executed, for security reason, only admin users can check this field must when this property is needed.

        &lt;b&gt;Storage page&lt;/b&gt;
        This option makes it possible to store your record in a storage page, for example a &quot;sysfolder&quot;, otherwise records are stored in the current page.
        When this option is used, records are fetched in the storage page and in the pages defined in the &quot;starting point&quot; if any.</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">
	</orig_hash>
	<orig_text type="array">
	</orig_text>
</T3locallang>