<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>sav_library</csh_table>
		<description>Default TCA_DESCR for extensions built with the SAV Library</description>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
      <label index="helpGeneral.description">Help for General Tab</label>
			<label index="helpGeneral.details">
        &lt;b&gt;Select form&lt;/b&gt;
         use this selector to select the form name. Let use recall that the "SAV Library" makes it possible to build several forms associated with the same extension, thus providing different views of your tables.

        &lt;b&gt;Show all if no filter&lt;/b&gt;
        If set, all items are displayed if no filter is applied, for example by means of the "sav_filter_abc" extension.
        
        &lt;b&gt;If no information available&lt;/b&gt;
        Use the selector to choose what to display when no information are available.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Max number of items&lt;/b&gt;
        Maximum number of items that will be displayed in a page. If set to 0, all items are displayed.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Help page&lt;/b&gt;
        Use this selector to choose a page of your site which will be use as an help page for your extension. In this case, an icon is displayed in the title bar of your extension.			
			</label>
			
      <label index="helpInput.description">Help for Input Tab</label>
			<label index="helpInput.details">
        &lt;b&gt;Input on form&lt;/b&gt;
        If set, Front End inputs are allowed.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Allowed groups&lt;/b&gt;
        If you select user groups, user must belong to one of these groups to be allowed to input data in the Front End.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Input Admin field&lt;/b&gt;
        Put here a field under the form "tablename.fieldname" (if you use only "fieldname", the main table is taken as "tablename").
        This will restrict the input to users that have "Admin" right for this field in their TS Config.
        For example, if one user has "extKey_Admin=value1,value2" in his TS Config, he will be allowed to edit or delete items for which "fieldname" is equal to "value1" or "value2" for the extension "extKey".
        The fields or the folders which have the attribute "editAdminPlus= 1;" can be modified if the user has the "Admin+"" rights. For example, if the TS Config is "extKey_Admin=value1+,value2" , the user is an "Admin+" for the records where "fieldname" is equal to "value1" and just "Admin" for the records where "fieldname" is equal to "value2".
        Users become "Super Admin" for the extension "extKey" their TS Config is "extKey_Admin=*"".

        &lt;b&gt;No "new" button&lt;/b&gt;
        No new button is added to the form. It means that you can modify existing records but you cannot create new record.
        
        &lt;b&gt;No "delete" button&lt;/b&gt;
        A delete button will not be added in front of the records in "show All" views.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Add a "delete" button only for records created by the user&lt;/b&gt;
        Clear isn't it !
        
        &lt;b&gt;Input start date&lt;/b&gt;
        If set,  inputs in the Front End will not be possible before this date.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Input end date&lt;/b&gt;
        If set, inputs in the Front End will not be possible after this date.

        &lt;b&gt;Apply date limit&lt;/b&gt;
        Use the selector to set either "Nobody", "All", "Admin plus users", "All excludind Super Admin". The date limit is applied according to this selector.
			</label>

      <label index="helpAdvanced.description">Help for Advanced Tab</label>
			<label index="helpAdvanced.details">
        &lt;b&gt;Permanent filter&lt;/b&gt;
        You can use this field to add a where clause that will be added to the where clause of the form query.

        &lt;b&gt;Add a fragment (# content id) to links&lt;/b&gt;
        The content id is added as a fragment to the links.
			</label>
			
		</languageKey>






	 <!-- FRENCH LANGUAGE SECTION -->

		<languageKey index="fr" type="array">

      <label index="helpGeneral.description">Aide pour l'onglet "Général"</label>
			<label index="helpGeneral.details">
        &lt;b&gt;Select form&lt;/b&gt;
         Utiliser ce sélecteur pour choisir le nom du formulaire. Rappelons que "SAV Library" permet de construire plusieurs formulaires associés à la même extension et, aisni, d'avoir des vues différentes des tables.

        &lt;b&gt;Show all if no filter&lt;/b&gt;
        En sélectionnant cette entrée, tous les items sont affichés quand aucun filtre n'est appliqué comme, par exemple, l'extension "sav_filter_abc".
        
        &lt;b&gt;If no information available&lt;/b&gt;
        Utiliser ce sélecteur pour choisir ce qui doit être affiché quand aucune information n'est disponible.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Max number of items&lt;/b&gt;
        Nombre maximum d'items qui seront affichés. Si la valeur 0 est utilisée, tous les items seront affichés.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Help page&lt;/b&gt;
        Utiliser ce sélecteur pour choisir une page de votre site qui sera utilisée comme page d'aide pour votre extension. Dans ce cas, une icône sera affichée dans la barre de titre de l'extension.			
			</label>
			
      <label index="helpInput.description">Aide pour l'onglet "Option de saisie"</label>
			<label index="helpInput.details">
        &lt;b&gt;Input on form&lt;/b&gt;
        En sélectionnant cette option, les entrées Front End sont autorisées.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Allowed groups&lt;/b&gt;
        Si vous sélectionnez des groupes d'utilisateurs, l'utilisateur de l'extension doit appartenir à l'un de ces groupes pour être autorisé à entrer des données en Front End.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Input Admin field&lt;/b&gt;
        Mettre dans ce champ une entrée de la forme "NomTable.NomChamp" (si vous utilisez seulement "NomChamp", la table principale définie dans la requête sera utilisée pour "NomTable),
        Ceci restreindra les entrées aux utilisateurs qui ont des droits "Admin" dans leur TS Config.
        Par exemple, si un utilisateur a "extKey_Admin=valeur1,valeur2" dans son TS Config, il sera autorisé à éditer et détruire les items pour lesquels "NomChamp" est égal à "valeur1" ou "valeur2" pour l'extension "extKey".
        Les champs ou les onglets pour lesquels "editAdminPlus = 1;" est utilisé pourront être modifé en Front End si l'utilisateur a les droits "Admin+". Par exemple, si son TS Config est "extKey_Admin=valeur+,valeur2" , l'utilisateur est "Admin+" pour les enregistrements où "nomChamp" est égal à "valeur2" et juste "Admin" pour les champs où "nomChamp" est égal à "valeur2".
        Les utilisateurs deviennent "Super Admin" pour l'extension extKey, si leur TS Config est "extKey_Admin=*"".

        &lt;b&gt;No "new" button&lt;/b&gt;
        Le bouton "Nouveau" ne sera pas ajouté au formulaire. Cela signifie que la modification d'enregistrements existants est possible mais que la création de nouveaux enregistrements est impossible.
        
        &lt;b&gt;No "delete" button&lt;/b&gt;
        Un bouton "supprimer" ne sera pas ajouté devant chaque enregistrement dans les vues "Show All".
        
        &lt;b&gt;Add a "delete" button only for records created by the user&lt;/b&gt;
        Ajoute un bouton "supprimer" seulemet pour les enregistrements créés par l'utilisateur.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Input start date&lt;/b&gt;
        Si ce champ est utilisé, les entrées en Front End ne seront pas possibles avant cette date.
        
        &lt;b&gt;Input end date&lt;/b&gt;
        Si ce champ est utilisé, les entrées en Front End ne seront pas possibles après cette date.

        &lt;b&gt;Apply date limit&lt;/b&gt;
        Utiliser ce sélecteur pour choisir "Personne", "Tous", "Utilisateurs Admin plus", "Tous sauf les Super Admin". La date limite est appliquée en fonction de ce sélecteur.
			</label>

      <label index="helpAdvanced.description">Aide pour l'onglet "Avancées"</label>
			<label index="helpAdvanced.details">
        &lt;b&gt;Permanent filter&lt;/b&gt;
        Vous pouvez utiliser ce champ pour ajouter une clause WHERE qui sera ajoutée à la clause WHERE de la requête associée au formulaire.

        &lt;b&gt;Add a fragment (# content id) to links&lt;/b&gt;
        L'id du contenu sera ajouté comme fragment à l'url des liens.
			</label>

		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>



